

# **Sharjeel Anjum**

UI UX Designer & Front end Developer

92 302 6198713

Islamabad, Pakistan



#### **About Me**

Hello, I'm Sharjeel Anjum. I Have 12 years of experience in UI & UX designer and Frontend Developer. I have worked on a variety of brands and with agencies both big and small.

A bright, talented, ambitious and self-motivated web designer with a strong technical background who possesses self-discipline and the ability to work with the minimum of supervision. Able to play a key role throughout a sites development to ensure maximum accessibility, customer experience and usability.

# **Education**

Matric 2005

**Intermediate** 2007 GOVT. DEGREE COLLEGE

2009 Bachelor Degree **GOVT. DEGREE COLLEGE** 

Web & Graphic 2009 **Designing Course** 

sharjil.hz@gmail.com www.sharjeelanjum.com

### **Work Experience**

### MediaLinkers 2012 - Present

Islamabad

# **UI UX Designer & Frontend** Developer

At Medialinkers my duties are to design prototypes, Branding, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, APP Design, React Native UI Screens, React IS

#### **Ociat**

2014 - 2018

Part Time - Freelance

# Senoir Web Designer & **Frontend Developer**

Working as a Part Time - Freelance with Ociat company, here my duties are, Web Design, Logo, HTML, CSS.

### ITSS PVT. LTD 2009 - 2012

Lahore

# Senoir Web Designer & **Graphic Designer**

Working with ITSS company, here my duties are, Web Design, Logo, Branding, HTML, CSS.

#### **Amoka** International

2009 - 2009

Lahore

# Web & Graphic Designer

Started My career as a internship at Amoka International in Lahore, Here i worked as web & graphic Designer, my duties was to design prototypes, Logo Design, Brochure Designs, Flash animations.

#### Skills

#### **Designing Skills**

Web Templates Designing

APP Design

Logo Designing

Flyer Designing

**Brochure Designing** 

Roll Up Banners

Brnading

illustration

Email templates designing

Posters

#### Front-end Development

HTML / HTML5

CSS / CSS3 / SASS

Bootstrap / Tailwind CSS

PSD to HTML

Javascript

iQuery

React Native

React JS

**Email Templates Publishing** 

Wordpress Theme integration

#### Tools















Portfolio Will be shown while interview on demand.